<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Aishwarya Pant&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://aishpant.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Aishwarya Pant&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 20:48:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aishpant.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>✍️What I learned while writing Go</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/what-i-learned-writing-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 20:48:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/what-i-learned-writing-go/</guid>
      <description>I have been writing Go for about 6 months now at my new job. Coming from a Java world, it is a joy to write Go. Some may call the language boring, because it is easy to learn and easy to write. This is precisely what I love the most about Go. There usually isn&amp;rsquo;t more than one way of achieving the same result.
If you are able to work through the gotour, I believe you should be able to understand 99% of the open source Go code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>outreachy : closing notes</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/outreachy-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 22:15:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/outreachy-recap/</guid>
      <description>This is the last week of my three-month internship with Outreachy.
Did I accomplish what I had set out to do? In some ways, yes. I have written a helper tool that tries to generate and formats sysfs style documentation. Link to the project - abi2doc.
From a rough estimate1, there are around 2000 attributes that are undocumented in the kernel. Using abi2doc, I have added documentation for 312 sysfs attributes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>offlineimap &#43; mutt = how to deal with LKML</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/mailing-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 22:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/mailing-lists/</guid>
      <description>LKML is a very high volume mailing list. I accumulate around 500 emails during the time I spend sleeping. It&amp;rsquo;s a kitchen sink for every kernel patch and discussion that is going on, which is a good thing and a bad thing. Because I care about only a few of them. Most users subscribe to and read only subsystem specific mailing lists. The trick is to run scripts on top of them to find the emails of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>attribute documentation : what, why, how?</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/attribute-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 15:01:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/attribute-documentation/</guid>
      <description>Before I talk about the title of the post, I will take a diversion to try to explain what kernel hackers mean when they say they do not break userspace.
What is an API and an ABI? API: Application Programming Interface
ABI: Application Binary Interface
The two terms are closely related and can be a source of confusion. Both APIs and ABIs specify how two components interact with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You should apply for Outreachy!</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/start-outreachy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 12:06:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/start-outreachy/</guid>
      <description>For the last three weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working as an Outreachy intern with Linux Kernel. Outreachy is an amazing three-month internship programme to get more underrepresented people to work on Free &amp;amp; Open Source Software (FOSS). It was started because of very low participation of women (less than 8%) in Google Summer of Code (GSoC). It&amp;rsquo;s completely remote and interns are paid $5,500 on completion of the project with an additional $500 stipend for attending conferences or meet-ups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am done reading Isaac Asimov</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/isaac-asimov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 02:29:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/isaac-asimov/</guid>
      <description>A review of I, Robot and The Caves of Steel, and the problematic characterisation of women.
 I have a huge problem with Asimov. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing that so many people who have read him are not talking about it. And it is in his characterization of women. That is, if they exist at all. There is one other Asimov I&amp;rsquo;ve read and that&amp;rsquo;s I, Robot. I admit, I enjoyed the short story collection a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review : The Three Body Problem</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/three-body-problem-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 02:17:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/three-body-problem-review/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR, 3.5 out of 5 stars
I really really wanted to like The Three Body Problem a lot more because of the numerous positive reviews I&amp;rsquo;ve been hearing. I thought it was very interesting (Gobbled it up in three days straight!). It was full of great ideas and very imaginative. The parts in which we enter the game simulation were so fun to read. It was unfortunate when the game came abruptly to an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preface : What have I been upto?</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/what-have-i-been-upto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 12:03:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/what-have-i-been-upto/</guid>
      <description>This is my last week at @Flipkart! Thursday- November 30th will be my last day of work, after which I go on a 4-month sabbatical. I will have to return all my IT assets including my beloved MacBook Pro :-(
Back to the Outreachy excitement! There are a lot of things I want to get done before the internship officialy starts on the December 5. I have started to maintain a journal of what I am going to be working on every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description> .left { float: left; padding: 0 20px 20px 0; } ul{list-style-position:inside;}   Hello! I am Aishwarya Pant, a Software Engineer at Flipkart. Currently, I am on a four month sabbatical to work on improving attribute documentation for the Linux kernel with Outreachy. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>