<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Outreachy on Aishwarya Pant</title>
    <link>https://aishpant.github.io/tags/outreachy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Outreachy on Aishwarya Pant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 22:15:34 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aishpant.github.io/tags/outreachy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>outreachy : closing notes</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/outreachy-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 22:15:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/outreachy-recap/</guid>
      <description>This is the last week of my three-month internship with Outreachy.
Did I accomplish what I had set out to do? In some ways, yes. I have written a helper tool that tries to generate and formats sysfs style documentation. Link to the project - attribute documentation.
As I mentioned in a previous post, the ABI documentation format looks like the following:
What: (the full sysfs path of the attribute)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>attribute documentation : what, why, how?</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/attribute-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 15:01:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/attribute-documentation/</guid>
      <description>Before I talk about the title of the post, I will take a diversion to try to explain what kernel hackers mean when they say they do not break userspace.
What is an API and an ABI? API: Application Programming Interface
ABI: Application Binary Interface
The two terms are closely related and can be a source of confusion. Both APIs and ABIs specify how two components interact with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You should apply for Outreachy!</title>
      <link>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/start-outreachy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 12:06:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aishpant.github.io/blog/start-outreachy/</guid>
      <description>For the last three weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working as an Outreachy intern with Linux Kernel. Outreachy is an amazing three-month internship programme to get more underrepresented people to work on Free &amp;amp; Open Source Software (FOSS). It was started because of very low participation of women (less than 8%) in Google Summer of Code (GSoC). It&amp;rsquo;s completely remote and interns are paid $5,500 on completion of the project with an additional $500 stipend for attending conferences or meet-ups.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>